thoora.com 2011-02-16

# Thoora.com | Privacy Policy

Thoora has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad, aggregated demographic information. Our site may use cookies to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for the other purposes set out below: 

We use cookies to remind us who you are and to find your account information in our database when you access a service so you do not need to log in at every visit. This helps us to provide you with service tailored to your specific needs and interests. A cookie is created when you register for a service. 

We use cookies to estimate our audience size. Your browser is given a unique cookie that helps us determine whether yours is a repeat visit or a first visit. 

We use cookies to determine the browser the visitor uses so the site can be designed to work properly with the most common versions of different browsers. 

Advertisers that place ads with thoora.com may use cookies. 

Our site's registration forms require users to give us your first name, last name, email address and password. Thoora.com does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. Thoora.com retains personal information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 

This site contains links to third party sites. Thoora.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Thoora.com co-branded sites and content partner sites may have privacy policies independent of thoora.com. This Privacy Policy extends only to data collected on pages hosted on thoora.com servers. Thoora.com may share aggregate information with trading partners, co-branded sites, and advertisers. However, this aggregated information does not contain personally identifiable information. 

Demographic and profile data is used to tailor our visitor's experience at our site and display the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis only. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and interception by third parties. Thoora.com assumes no liability for interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet. 

## Children’s Guidelines

This site is not marketed to or directed towards children. Nevertheless, it is possible for children to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent within chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. No communication, however, will be sent to anyone or information collected from anyone who indicates that they are younger than 16 years old without their parents' permission. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact: [info@thoora.com](mailto:info@thoora.com)

(Last Revised: September 15, 2009)
